I think it's completely nonsensical. The
LLM is not running in your Python
process. The universe would end before
Python could execute inference. So, the
LLM is a very, very simple HTTP call
away. So, it's utterly baffling to me
that people think any particular
language has a natural advantage to make
what is an incredibly simple HTTP call.
Open close not written in Python.
>> [music]
>> In the case of many enterprise
applications, they're obviously written
in Java. The critical adjacencies or
existing business logic, existing
enterprise services those applications
interact with, and it's quite obvious
the correct thing to do is simply make
the very simple HTTP calls from your
Java stack.
The AI Native Dev is a podcast for
developers and engineering leads at the
cutting edge of AI and agentic coding.
Join your hosts Guy Pajani [music] and
me, Simon Maple, every week as we chat
with the most exciting voices in AI and
tackle the biggest questions facing
developers today.
This is the AI Native Dev.